Guide to the Gotham Inc. Records, 1967-1997 and undated RL.00468
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1973-1996 and undated, 129 boxes
  - Major Clients, 1973-1996 and undated
    - Drackett,1975-1995 and undated
      - Renuzit (continued), 1990-1993 (Box 68)
        - 1172. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Renuzit Fragrance Jars. BMZP 1253 1992 Beautiful New Shapes :30. 1992 (Box 68)
        - 1173. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Drackett Co. Renuzit Fragrance Jars. 1992 Beautiful New Shapes; BMZP 1253 :30; BMZP 1265 :15. 1992 (Box 68)
        - 1174. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Renuzit Fragrance Jars. BMZP 1253 Renuzit Fragrance Jars :30; BMZP 1265 1992 Beautiful New Shapes :15. 1992 (Box 68)
        - 1175. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Renuzit Fragrance Jars. 1992 Beautiful New Shapes": BMZP 1253 :30; BMZP 1235 :15. 1992 (Box 68)
        - 1176. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Renuzit Electric Long Last. BMRU 3023 Lasts A Long Long Time :30; BMRU 3035 Lasts A Long Long Time :15. 1993 (Box 68)
        - 1177. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Renuzit Electric Long Last. BMRU 3023 Lasts A Long Long Time :30; BMRU 3035 Lasts A Long Long Time :15. 1993 (Box 68)
      - Renuzit (continued), 1993-1995 (Box 69)
        - 1178. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Renuzit Electric Long Last. BMRU 3023 Lasts A Long Long Time :30; BMRU 3035 Lasts A Long Long Time :15. 1993 (Box 69)
        - 1179. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Renuzit Electric Long Last. BMRU 3023 Lasts A Long Long Time :30; BMRU 3035 Lasts A Long Long Time :15. 1993 (Box 69)
        - 1180. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Renuzit Electric Long Last. BMRU 3023 Lasts A Long Long Time :30; BMRU 3035 Lasts A Long Long Time :15. 1993 (Box 69)
        - 1181. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Drackett Co. Renuzit Fresh And Dry. BMFD 5383 Hit by an Odor First Dry Spray :30. 1993 (Box 69)
        - 1182. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Renuzit Electric Long Last. BMRU 3023 Lasts A Long Long Time :30; BMRU 3035 Lasts A Long Long Time :15. 1993 (Box 69)
        - 1183. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Renuzit Electric Long Last. BMRU 3023 Lasts A Long Long Time :30; BMRU 3035 Lasts A Long Long Time :15. 1993 (Box 69)
        - 1184. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Renuzit. Banquet :30 Rev. 2. 1994 (Box 69)
        - 1185. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial. Renuzit. 5-30 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1994 (Box 69)
        - 1186. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Renuzit Electric Long Last. 5 Spots. 1994 (Box 69)
        - 1187. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial. Renuzit. Slugger's Ver. 2 :30; Half a Car Ver.2 :30. 1994 (Box 69)
        - 1188. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial Dishwashing Liquid/Renuzit In-Vent. Real People Ver. 1 Rev. :30; Germs are Everywhere Rev. :30; Half a Car :25. 1994 (Box 69)
        - 1189. Gotham Inc. Dial. Renuzit New Naturals. XYLC 5393 Boutique :23. 1995 (Box 69)
        - 1190. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Dial. Renuzit. NFA Agency Vers. Half a Car :30. 1995 (Box 69)
        - 1191. Gotham Inc. Dial. Renuzit New Naturals. XYLC 5393 Boutique :23. 1995 (Box 69)
        - 1192. Gotham Inc. Dial. Renuzit Long Last Mist. XYLC 5013 Brick :30. 1995 (Box 69)
        - 1193. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Renuzit In-Vent. Half a Car. 1995 (Box 69)
      - Renuzit (continued), Undated (Box 70)
        - 1194. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Renuzit Adjustable. BMRS 5033 Newlywed Alt. Rev.1 :30; BMRS 5013 Lost it With Renuzit :30. Undated (Box 70)
        - 1195. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson.Bristol Myers. Renuzit Roommates. 6 Spots. See Enclosed List. Undated (Box 70)
        - 1196. Renuzit Roommates. BMRM 6293 Hunk Rev.2 :30. Undated (Box 70)
      - Vanish (also a Bristol-Myers product), 1976-1983 and Undated
        - 1197. Vanish. 6 Spots. See Enclosed List. Undated (Box 70)
        - 1198. Bristol Myers. Automatic Vanish. BMVA 2023 No Substitute :30. Undated (Box 70)
        - 1199. Kenyon & Eckhardt. Liquid Vanish. Mrs. Byebe CBS :30; Mrs. Byebe ABC :30; Crystal Vanish. Meets the Eye demo :30. Undated (Box 70)
        - 1200. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. 6-30 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. Undated (Box 70)
        - 1201. Vanish. Bowl Brite. 12 Spots. See Enclosed List. Undated (Box 70)
        - 1202. Drackett Co. Liquid Vanish. Mrs. Bybee; Mrs. Oliver; Give me Ten Seconds". Undated (Box 70)
        - 1203. Crystal Vanish. 12 Spots. See Enclosed List. Undated (Box 70)
        - 1204. Bristol Myers. Liquid Vanish. BMLV 6023 Talk About Thick Rev. :30. Undated (Box 70)
        - 1205. Laurence Charles Free. Drackett Co. Poly shine. TV Monitor A; TV Monitor B. 1982 (Box 70)
        - 1206. Kenyon & Eckhardt. Bristol Myers. Vanish. BMVA 3183 Whistle-Germ Demo :30. 1983 (Box 70)
        - 1207. Kenyon & Eckhardt. Drackett Co. Folding Box Rev. w/Top Super; Folding Box Rev. w/Bottom Super; Lady Rev. W/new Audio. 1983 (Box 70)
      - Vanish (continued), 1984-1987 (Box 71)
        - 1208. Vanish. 5 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1984 (Box 71)
        - 1209. Bristol Myers. Vanish. BMVN 4043 The Difference/Crystal & liquid :30. 1984 (Box 71)
        - 1210. Kenyon & Eckhardt. Bristol Myers. Vanish Liquid Crystal. BMVE 4031 :10. 1984 (Box 71)
        - 1211. Kenyon & Eckhardt. Vanish Bowl Brite. BMEV 4103 :30. 1984 (Box 71)
        - 1212. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Vanish. BMVN 5091 Talking Toilets/ID :10; BMAV 5152 Talking Toilets/20 Mortisse :20. 1985 (Box 71)
        - 1213. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Vanish. BMVN 5091 Talking Toilets/ID :10; BMAV 5152 Talking Toilets/20 Mortisse :20. 1985 (Box 71)
        - 1214. Vanish. BMAV 5053 Talking toilets". Undated (Box 71)
        - 1215. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Automatic vanish. Talking Toilets Male/Demo :30. 1985 (Box 71)
        - 1216. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Automatic vanish. Talking Toilets Male/Demo :30. 1985 (Box 71)
        - 1217. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Vanish Bowl Brite. 4-30 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1985 (Box 71)
        - 1218. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Automatic Vanish. BMAV 5063 Talking Toilets/Super Clean w/Mortisse :30. 1985 (Box 71)
        - 1219. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Automatic Vanish. BMAV 5243 Soldier :30. 1986 (Box 71)
        - 1220. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Vanish. BMVN 6202 Mugsy :20. 1986 (Box 71)
        - 1221. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Vanish. BMAV 2033 Quartet Animated rev.; BMVN 4043 The Difference/Crystal & Liquid; BMEV 4103 Lady/Arcub Brush Rev. 1. 1986 (Box 71)
        - 1222. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Vanish. BMVN 7223 Soldier/Tag Rev. :30. 1987 (Box 71)
        - 1223. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Vanish Drop Ins. BMVR 6073 Bowl Brothers :30. 1987 (Box 71)
      - Vanish (continued), 1987 (Box 72)
        - 1224. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Vanish. BMVN 7253 The Bowl Brothers Rev.2 :30. 1987 (Box 72)
        - 1225. Mistral. Vanish. :30 English. 1987 (Box 72)
        - 1226. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Vanish Drop Ins. BMVR 7123 Bowl Brothers Rev.2 :30. 1987 (Box 72)
        - 1227. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Vanish. BMQA 7033 Shoot Out :30; BMQA 7083 Outer Space :30. 1987 (Box 72)
        - 1228. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Automatic Vanish. BMVN 7243 Soldier/Tag Rev. 1 :30. 1987 (Box 72)
        - 1229. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Vanish Drop Ins. BMVR 7143 Bowl Brothers Rev.3 :30. 1987 (Box 72)
        - 1230. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Vanish. BMQA 7083 Outer Space :30. 1987 (Box 72)
        - 1231. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Dual Action Liquid Vanish. BMQA 7123 Shoot out Rev. :30. 1987 (Box 72)
        - 1232. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Vanish. BMQA 7083 Outer Space :30. 1987 (Box 72)
        - 1233. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Automatic Vanish/Vanish Drop Ins. 5 Spots. See Enclosed List. Undated (Box 72)
        - 1234. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Vanish Drop Ins. BMVR 7143 Bowl Brothers Rev. 3 :30. 1987 (Box 72)
        - 1235. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Automatic Vanish. BMVN 7243 Soldier/Tag Rev.1 :30. 1987 (Box 72)
        - 1236. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Vanish. BMVN 7273 The Bowl Brothers rev.3 :20/:10. 1987 (Box 72)
        - 1237. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Vanish. BMVN 7293 The Bowl Brothers rev.5 :20/:10. 1987 (Box 72)
        - 1238. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Vanish. BMVN 7293 The Bowl Brothers rev.5 :20/:10. 1987 (Box 72)
        - 1239. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Vanish. BMQA 7083 Outer Space :30. 1987 (Box 72)
        - 1240. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Vanish Drop Ins. BMVR 7143 Bowl Brothers rev.3 :30. 1987 (Box 72)
      - Vanish (continued), 1988 (Box 73)
        - 1241. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Dual Action Liquid Vanish. BMAQ 8185 Duke/Demo :15. 1988 (Box 73)
        - 1242. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Dual Action Liquid Vanish. BMAQ 8165 The Duke :15. 1988 (Box 73)
        - 1243. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Dual Action Liquid Vanish.Comtrex AS. BMJR 8013 The Duke OC/Dreaming Lady :15. 1988 (Box 73)
        - 1244. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Dual Action Liquid Vanish. BMAQ 7153 Flush Tones/Duke :30. 1988 (Box 73)
        - 1245. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Vanish Line. BMVN 7303 Flush Tones Duke :30. 1988 (Box 73)
        - 1246. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Grey Adv. Bristol Myers. Dual Action Liquid Vanish./Drano Liquid. BMFG 8023 Duke Demo/Splish Splash :30. 1988 (Box 73)
        - 1247. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Vanish. BBMVR 8155 Bowl Bro... :15. 1988 (Box 73)
        - 1248. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Dual Action Liquid Vanish. BMAQ 8185 Duke/Demo :15. 1988 (Box 73)
        - 1249. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Dual Action Liquid Vanish. BMAQ 8165. 1988 (Box 73)
        - 1250. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Dual Action Liquid Vanish. 4-30 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1988 (Box 73)
        - 1251. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Dual Action Liquid Vanish. Flush Tones/Duke. Non-New Lysol :30; New Lysol :30; Different Audio :30. 1988 (Box 73)
        - 1252. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Vanish. BMVR 8155 Bowl Bro. :15; BMAQ 8165 The Duke :15--:14 music track. 1988 (Box 73)
        - 1253. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Dual Action Vanish. Flush Tones/Duke. Non-New Lysol :30. 1988 (Box 73)
        - 1254. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Dual Action Vanish. Flush Tones/Duke. Non-New Lysol :30. 1988 (Box 73)
        - 1255. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Dual Action Vanish. Flush Tones/Duke. DMJ 5313 Tucker/No Demo :30. 1988 (Box 73)
        - 1256. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Dual Action Vanish. 4-30 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1988 (Box 73)
      - Vanish (continued), 1988-1990 (Box 74)
        - 1257. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Vanish. BMVR 8155 Bowl Bro. :15. 1988 (Box 74)
        - 1258.Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Dual Action Liquid Vanish. BMAQ 7153 Flush Tones/Duke :30. 1988 (Box 74)
        - 1259. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Vanish Line. BMVN 9353 KG Bowl/Foamin' 20/10 :30. 1989 (Box 74)
        - 1260. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Vanish Drop Ins. BMVR 7143 Bowl Brothers Rev. 3; Automatic Vanish. BMAV 7303 As The Bowl Flushes; Dual Action Vanish. Flush Tones Duke/No Demo :30 each. 1989 (Box 74)
        - 1261. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Vanish Line. BMVN 9353 KG Bowl/Foamin' 20/10 :30. 1989 (Box 74)
        - 1262. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Vanish Line. BMVN 9353 KG Bowl/Foamin' 20/10 :30. 1989 (Box 74)
        - 1263. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Vanish Line. BMIN 9053 Johnny Clean :30; BMIN 9065 Johnny Clean :15. 1989 (Box 74)
        - 1264. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Vanish Line. BMVN 9333 Johnny Clean :20/10. 1989 (Box 74)
        - 1265. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Vanish Foamin'. BMIN 9053 Johnny Clean Rev. :30; BMIN 9065 Johnny Clean Rev. :15; BMVN 9343 Johnny Clean Alt./Foamin'/VDI :30. 1989 (Box 74)
        - 1266. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Vanish Line. BMVN 9333 Johnny Clean :20/10. 1989 (Box 74)
        - 1267. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Vanish Foamin'. BMIN 9053 Johnny Clean Rev. :30; BMIN 9065 Johnny Clean Rev. :15; BMVN 9343 Johnny Clean Alt./Foamin'/VDI :30. 1989 (Box 74)
        - 1268. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Vanish Line. BMVN 9353 KG Bowl :30. 1989 (Box 74)
        - 1269. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Vanish Line. BMVN 9343 Johnny Clean Alt. Foamin'/VDI :30. 1989 (Box 74)
        - 1270. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Automatic Vanish. BMAN 8313 KG Bowl-New :30. 1989 (Box 74)
        - 1271. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Vanish Foamin'. BMIN 9065 Johnny Clean Rev. :15. 1989 (Box 74)
        - 1272. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Vanish Drop Ins. BMVR 0233 Western Bowl Rev. Mix :30. 1990 (Box 74)
      - Vanish (continued), 1990-1993 (Box 75)
        - 1273. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Vanish Drop Ins. BMVR 0233 Western Bowl Rev. Mix :30. 1990 (Box 75)
        - 1274. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Vanish Drop Ins. BMVR 9163 I Want Some V-A-N-I-S-H :30. 1990 (Box 75)
        - 1275. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Vanish Line. BMVN 9373 Holly Wood bowl :30. 1990 (Box 75)
        - 1276. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Vanish Line. BMVN 1433 Beetle Bailey Volunteers rev. 2 :31. 1991 (Box 75)
        - 1277. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Vanish Line. BMVN 1433 Beetle Bailey Volunteers rev. 2 :31. 1991 (Box 75)
        - 1278. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Vanish Historical Reel. 1991 (Box 75)
        - 1279. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Vanish Line. BMVN 0423 Beetle Bailey Rev. Volunteers. 1991 (Box 75)
        - 1280. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Vanish Drop Ins. 5-30 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1991 (Box 75)
        - 1281. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Vanish Mildew Plus. Grungies/Dingies :30. 1992 (Box 75)
        - 1282. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Vanish Mildew Plus. BMVX 2139 Hiding' :25. 1992 (Box 75)
        - 1283. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Vanish Power Packs. BMVG 2023 The Dirt and Stains Alt. :30. 1992 (Box 75)
        - 1284. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Vanish Power Packs. BMVG 2023 The Dirt And Stains Alt. :30. 1992 (Box 75)
        - 1285. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Vanish Clear Drop Ins. BMVJ 1115 The Bathroom Blues :15. 1992 (Box 75)
        - 1286. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers. Vanish Drop Ins. BMVR 2293 Vanish Bathroom Bowl Buildup Rev. :30. 1992 (Box 75)
        - 1287. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Vanish Mildew Plus. BMVX 2169 Hiding Non-New :25. 1993 (Box 75)
        - 1288. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Vanish Mildew Plus. 4 spots. See Enclosed List. 1993 (Box 75)
      - Vanish (continued), 1993 (Box 76)
        - 1289. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Vanish Mildew Plus. 4 spots. See Enclosed List. 1993 (Box 76)
        - 1290. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Vanish Line. Bowl Brothers :30; As the Bowl Flushes :30; Duke-No Demo :30. 1993 (Box 76)
        - 1291. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Vanish Mildew Plus. BMVX 2169 Hiding Non-New :25. 1993 (Box 76)
        - 1292. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Vanish Clear Drop Ins. Bathroom Blues/Non-New. 1993 (Box 76)
        - 1293. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Vanish Clear Drop Ins. Bathroom Blues/Non-New. 1993 (Box 76)
        - 1294. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Vanish Mildew Plus. 4 spots. See Enclosed List. 1993 (Box 76)
      - Windex, 1980, 1991
        - 1295. Bristol Myers. Kitchen Shine. BMWK 0093 Clouds :30. 1980 (Box 76)
        - 1296. Daniel & Charles. Clouds I-VI. 1980 (Box 76)
        - 1297. Daniel & Charles. Windex Kitchen Shine. BMWK 0133 Clouds/Nozzle :30. 1980 (Box 76)
        - 1298. Daniel & Charles. Bristol Myers. Windex Kitchen Shine. BMWK 0103 Magic Bottle :30. 1980 (Box 76)
        - 1299. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Professional Strength Windex. 92 lb. Women/Non-New :15. 1991 (Box 76)
        - 1300. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Professional Strength Windex. BMVW 1025 92 lb. Women/Non Flip :15. 1991 (Box 76)
        - 1301. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Professional Strength Windex. BMVW 1013 92 lb. Women/Flip :30. 1991 (Box 76)
        - 1302. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Drackett Co. Professional Strength Windex. 4 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1991 (Box 76)
        - 1303. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Drackett Co. Windex. 5-30 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1991 (Box 76)
        - 1304. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Professional Strength Windex. BMVW 1013 92 Lb. Women/Flip :30. 1991 (Box 76)
        - 1305. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Professional Strength Windex. BMVW 1025 92 Lb. Women/Non-Flip :15. 1991 (Box 76)
      - Windex (continued), 1991-1993 (Box 77)
        - 1306. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Professional Strength Windex. BMVW 1013 92 Lb. Women/Flip :30. 1991 (Box 77)
        - 1307. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Drackett Co. Professional Strength Windex. Professional Cleaners of America. 1991 (Box 77)
        - 1308. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Drackett Co. Professional Strength Windex. 5-30 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1991 (Box 77)
        - 1309. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Extra Strength Windex. 5 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1991 (Box 77)
        - 1310. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Professional Strength Windex. BMVW 2143 Skyscraper Ver. 5R :30. 1992 (Box 77)
        - 1311. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Professional Strength Windex. BMVW 2143 Skyscraper Ver 5R :30. 1992 (Box 77)
        - 1312. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Drackett Co. Clear Windex. The Tougher The Test :30; Scent-Sational :30; Bless you Windex/New Improved :30. 1992 (Box 77)
        - 1313. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Professional Strength Windex. BMVW 2143 Skyscraper Ver. 5R :30. 1992 (Box 77)
        - 1314. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Windex. BMWI 2023 Magic #2 :30; BMWI 2043 Bye Bye Strikes Again :30; BMWI 2013 The Streak Strikes Again Ver. B :30. 1992 (Box 77)
        - 1315. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Windex. BMWI 2013 The Streak Strikes Ver. B :30; BMWI 2023 Magic 2 :30; BMWI 2043 Bye Bye Streaks :30. 1992 (Box 77)
        - 1316. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Bristol Myers Squibb. Windex. BMWI 2053 Magic :30. 1992 (Box 77)
        - 1317. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Drackett Co. Clear Windex. The Tougher The Test :30; Scent-Sational :30; Bless you Windex/New Improved :30. 1992 (Box 77)
        - 1318. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Windex. JSWI 3230 Magic Rev.1 :30. 1993 (Box 77)
        - 1319. Laurence Charles Free and Lawson. Windex. JSWI 3230 Magic Rev.1 :30. 1993 (Box 77)
      - Carpet Works, 1981
        - 1320. Drackett Co. Carpet Works. BMWO 1043A Two Jobs/New Pull Back; BMWO 1043 Two Jobs Pull Back. 1981 (Box 77)
        - 1321. Daniel & Charles. Drackett Co. Carpet Works. BMWO 1013 Two Jobs :30; BMWO 1013A Two Jobs :30. 1981 (Box 77)
    - GAF Corporation,1974-1978 and undated
      - Commercials, 1974-1977 (Box 78)
        - 1322. Mormar. GAF. GAFL 4272 :25; GAFL 4252 :25. 1974 (Box 78)
        - 1323. Daniel & Charles. GAF Siding. GAVV 5053 Vanguard Vinyl Siding :30. 1975 (Box 78)
        - 1324. Daniel & Charles. GAF View Master. GAVM 5403 See A Story :30. 1975 (Box 78)
        - 1325. GAF. Roofing and Siding. Super 8 Sound Sys. :30; GARS 5033 New House :30; GACP 5733 Clown :30. 1975 (Box 78)
        - 1326. GAF. Print Express. 7 Spots. 1975 (Box 78)
        - 1327. Daniel & Charles. GAF. GAVM 5423 Rear Screen Projection Adults :30; GAVM 543 Rear Screen Projection Kids :30. 1975 (Box 78)
        - 1328. Mormar. GAF. GAVM 5453 RSP/Kids rev. 2 :30. 1975 (Box 78)
        - 1329. Daniel & Charles. GAF Viewmaster. GAVM 5443 Rear Screen Projection Kids Rev. :30. 1975 (Box 78)
        - 1330. Daniel & Charles. GAF Print Express. GAPE 5753 Print Express/Indiana :30. 1975 (Box 78)
        - 1331. Daniel & Charles. GAF. GAWN 6013 WNCN :30. 1976 (Box 78)
        - 1332. Mormar. GAF. GAVM 6503 Basset :30. 1976 (Box 78)
        - 1333. GAF Show Reel 7 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1976 (Box 78)
        - 1334. GAF. 6 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1976 (Box 78)
        - 1335. Mormar. GAF. GACP 6853 File & Drum :30; GASP 6883 Double Image DLR. :30. 1976 (Box 78)
        - 1336. Daniel & Charles. GAF Viewmaster. GAVM 7553 Calendar Click :30; GAVM 7543 The Click :30. 1977 (Box 78)
        - 1337. Daniel & Charles. GAF. Chef :60. 1977 (Box 78)
        - 1338. Daniel & Charles. GAF. Brite-Bond Flooring. GAFL 7443 Rhyme & reason :30. 1977 (Box 78)
      - Commercials (continued), 1977-1978 (Box 79)
        - 1339. Daniel & Charles. GAF. GAVM 7513 Talking Viewmaster :30; GAVM 7523 Spiderman :30 Billy. 1977 (Box 79)
        - 1340. Daniel & Charles. Viewmaster. GAVM 8583 Disney Favorite Gift Pack :30. 1978 (Box 79)
        - 1341. GAF. Viewmaster Alternate :30; GAVM 8603 Spiderman. 1978 (Box 79)
        - 1342. GAF. Gafstar Sheet Vinyl. GAFL 8542 Fiesta Sale/Alt :30. 1978 (Box 79)
        - 1343. Daniel & Charles. GAF. Viewmaster. GAVM 8563. 1978 (Box 79)
        - 1344. Daniel & Charles. GAF. 10 Animatics. See Enclosed List. 1978 (Box 79)
        - 1345. Daniel & Charles. GAVM 8573 Viewmaster Spacement theater. 1978 (Box 79)
        - 1346. Daniel & Charles. GAF. Best Friend :30; Do it :30; Surprise :30. 1978 (Box 79)
        - 1347. GAF. GAFL 7532 Fiesta Sale/Rev. 1978 (Box 79)
        - 1348. Daniel & Charles. GAF. Surprise Rev. Vers. 3 & 4. 1978 (Box 79)
        - 1349. Mormar. GAF. GAFL 7472 Palazzo DHR :30. 1978 (Box 79)
        - 1350. Daniel & Charles. GAF. GAVV 8063 Vanguard Vinyl/Siding Vers. 3 :30. 1978 (Box 79)
        - 1351. GAF Floor. GAFL 8633 Surprise Rev. :30. 1978 (Box 79)
        - 1352. GAF. Talking Viewmaster-Spiderman :30; Calendar Click :30; Full One Hour Reel. Undated (Box 79)
        - 1353. GAF. Good Riddance. Undated (Box 79)
        - 1354. Daniel & Charles. GAF. GAFL 8612 Friend/Dealer; GAFL 8622 Surprise/Dealer :30 each. Undated (Box 79)
        - 1355. GAF Vinyl Sidings. Neighbors :30. 1978 (Box 79)
    - Gorton's Food (division of General Mills),1976-1995 and undated
      - Commercials, 1976-1981 (Box 80)
        - 1356. Mormar. Gortons Pull Back. GORT 6603 Pull Back :30. 1976 (Box 80)
        - 1357. Daniel & Charles. Gortons. GORT 7683 Survey :30. 1977 (Box 80)
        - 1358. Gortons. BOSP 8743 Nobody :30. Undated (Box 80)
        - 1359. Daniel & Charles. Gortons Fried Fish. BOSP 8743 Nobody :30; BOSP 8733 Whisper :30; BOSP 8723 Big Box :30. 1979 (Box 80)